{
	"name":"Udyr",
	"cards":[
		{
			"question":"What are udyr's four stances?",
			"answer":"Tiger, Turtle, Bear, and Phoenix"
		},
		{
			"question":"What role is udyr most often played in?",
			"answer":"Jungle"
		},
		{
			"question":"Is Udyr a melee or ranged champion?",
			"answer":"melee"
		},
		{
			"question":"who is the most streamer who plays udyr?",
			"answer":"Trick2g"
		},
		{
			"question":"what is a nickname for udyr?",
			"answer":"The Godyr"
		},
		{
			"question":"what style of play does udyr excel at?",
			"answer":"Splitpushing"
		},
		{
			"question":"what is considered a core item to build on udyr?",
			"answer":"Triforce"
		},
		{
			"question":"in what season was udyr the strongest?",
			"answer":"Season 6"
		},
		{
			"question":"what is the best skin for udyr?",
			"answer":"Spirit Gaurd Udyr (SGU)"
		},
		{
			"question":"should people main udyr?",
			"answer":"no"
		}
	]
}